

Jesse Wells

designer + developer

jessewells.com/portfolio

About

Web Designer & Developer based in Brooklyn NY with 6+ years of work experience in digital and print design, front-end design and front-end development

Likes

Vectors, SVG, Bezier Curves and everything Scalable & Losless.

Web Components, Web Animation, Server Side Javascript.

PC, Microsoft, Adobe CC, Vue.js, Visual Studio Code, Pug, Stylus.

Contact

1263 Broadway Brooklyn NY 11221

jessenwells@gmail.com

347 243 5863



jessenwells



jessenwells

Work Experience

Modell's Sporting Goods Front-end Developer

2015 - current

Assisted in all areas to redesign and relaunch the new E-Commerce Website including migration of platforms from MarketLive to DemandWare.

Developed Automated and Streamlined

Workflows, Site Specs, Style Guides and

Modern Email Templates.

Press Design

2010 - 2015

Lead Designer

Web Design, UI Design, Front-End Dev, Wordpress, Ecommerce, Web Ads, Print Design, Branding, Apparel

Graphics, Illustration, Print Ads.

Mammoth Advertising

2015 - 2016

Freelance

HTML5 Developer

Created animated interactive advertisments for web and display.
Assisted in transition from flash to html5.

Everyday Media

2014 - 2015

Freelance

Digital Marketing Designer

Created and managed facebook ads, pages and weekly headers.

Social media promotional images.
Print ads, web ads, and HTML emails.

F5 Interactive Agency

2012 - 2015

Freelance

Front-end Design and Development

Worked on various projects creating front end templates including complex UI, interactive data, infographics and

 \odot \odot \odot \bigcirc

Bootstrap / Foundation

Output

Description:

large scale animations.

Sass / Scss

Education

Fashion Institute of Technology

BFA - Illustration

Woocommerce

PHP / MySQL

Skills

Adobe Illustrator	\odot \odot \odot \odot	HTML5/CSS3
Adobe Photoshop	\odot	Javascript
Adobe InDesign	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bigcirc$	jQuery
Adobe After Effects	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bigcirc$	Node js
Adobe XD	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bigcirc$	Vuejs
Android Studio	\odot	Angular/MEAN
Wordpress	\odot \odot \odot \odot	Polymer